hometownlocator.com 2006-03-27

# HomeTownLocator Privacy Policy

[Home](http://www.hometownlocator.com/)  > Previous Page  > Privacy Policy

Welcome! This is one of a family of related HomeTownLocator sites owned by HTL, Inc. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of information that you may provide via this or related sites.

When you browse through our site, we collect:

  * basic information from your Internet browser about your computer and connection to ensure that we can provide the information requested
  * aggregate information on what pages are accessed to improve our site for your use

Cookies  
We use Session cookies to aid in navigation. We do not store any personal data in cookies. You may set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse cookies altogether, but certain features of this site might not work without session (temporary) cookies.

This site may have areas that require registration in order for you to benefit from specified features such as "Remind-Me" notices about events and ability to submit a classified ad or to post a comment in the public forums.

If you choose the free individual Membership, we will ask you to provide:

  * a user name and password for access to features and for updating your information
  * your e-mail address to ensure that the registration is a valid one

If you choose a Business Membership, we will ask you for more information including: 

  * a user name and password for access to features and for updating your information
  * business name, address and telephone number 
  * your e-mail address 
  * billing information

Changing and Updating personal information  
Members may change their personal information at any time by accessing the membership area of the site. You can change your e-mail address and password or any business information which has changed. 

Sharing of Information  
We will not make any personally identifiable information you provide to HTL, Inc. available to any third parties unless required to do so by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations.

Security  
This site takes reasonable steps to protect personally identifiable information as you transmit it to our site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure. 

Links to other Web Sites  
This site may contain links or references to other Web sites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy of every Web site you visit. 

How to Contact Us  
If you have any questions, comments, requests, or concerns related to this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this site, or if you would like to opt out of future communications, please contact us. 

Changes to This Privacy Policy  
If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this site. Please check back periodically. This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 1, 2003.
